{
  "id": 1001,
  "themeId": 10,
  "name": "Writing and Reading boulangerie Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say “bread”?",
      "options": [
        "Pan",
        "Pain",
        "Paine",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pain",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"baker\"? (masculine)",
      "options": [
        "Boulangère",
        "Boulanger",
        "Boulangé",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Boulanger",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"pastry shop\"?",
      "options": [
        "Patisserie",
        "Patiserie",
        "Boulangerie",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Patisserie",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “chocolate bread”?",
      "options": [
        "Pain au chocolat",
        "Painochocolat",
        "Pain chocolat",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pain au chocolat",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “raisin bread”?",
      "options": [
        "Pain au raisin",
        "Pain aux raisines",
        "Pain aux raisins",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pain aux raisins",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “lemon tart”?",
      "options": [
        "Tarte au citron",
        "Tarte aù citron",
        "Tarte aux citrons",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Tarte au citron",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “apple tart”?",
      "options": [
        "Tarte au pomme",
        "Tarte de pommes",
        "Tarte aux pommes",
        "Tarte des pommes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Tarte aux pommes",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"here is your change”?",
      "options": [
        "Voilà votre monnaie.",
        "Votre monnaie.",
        "Voilà la monnaie.",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you ask \"anything else/is that all\"?",
      "options": [
        "Ce sera tout ?",
        "Ce sera toute ?",
        "Ceux sera tout ?",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ce sera tout ?",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you order a baguette?",
      "options": [
        "Une baguette s’il vous plait ?",
        "Puis-je avoir une baguette s’il vous plait ?",
        "Est-ce que vous avez une baguette s’il vous plait ?",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}